let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Choose the operator which cannot be overloaded.",
        answer: "::",
        options: [
            "/",
            "()",
            "::",
            "%"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "A user defined header file is included by following statement in general.",
        answer: "#include “file.h”",
        options: [
            "#include “file.h”",
            "#include <fille.h>",
            "#include <file>",
            "#include <bits/stdcfile.h>"

        ]
    }, {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Identify the incorrect  constructor type.",
        answer: "friend constructor",
        options: [
            "friend constructor",
            "default constructor",
            "perameterized  constructor",
            "copy constructor"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is a constant that contains a single character enclosed within single quotes?",
        answer: "Character",
        options: [
            "Character",
            "Numeric",
            "Fixed",
            "Floating point"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 5,
        question: "	Delaration a pointer more than once may cause____",
        answer: "Trap",
        options: [
            "Error",
            "Abort",
            "Trap",
            "Null"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which one is not a correct variable type in C++?",
        answer: "real",
        options: [
            "float",
            "real",
            "int",
            "double"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "	In CPP, members of a class are ______ by default.",
        answer: "private",
        options: [
            "public",
            "protected",
            "static",
            "private"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: " In C++ Program, inline fuctions are expanded during _____",
        answer: "Run Time",
        options: [
            "Compile Time",
            "Run Time",
            "Debug Time",
            "Coding Time"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Default constructor has ____ arguments.",
        answer: "No argument",
        options: [
            "No argument",
            "One Argument",
            "Two Argument",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " Which class allows only one object to be created.",
        answer: " Sigleton Class",
        options: [
            "Nuclear Family Class",
            "Abstruct Class",
            "Sigleton Class",
            "Numero Uno Class"
        ]
    },

];